THE NEW YORK STATE TENANTS & NEIGHBORS COALITION RECORDS (APAP198) 1970-2002
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- New York State Housing Authorities, 1973-2000, Undated; 2; 4.6
  - Conciliation and Appeals Board (CAB) Mailings and Newsclippings, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - DHCR Legislative Proposal, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Rent Stabilization Association Code, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Council of the City of New York, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Rend Stabilization Issues, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - RSA Lawsuits, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - RSA Lawsuits, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - RSA Lawsuits, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - State Of New York Mortgage Agency, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - RSA Advertisements, 1980-1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - RSA Advertisements, 1980-1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - RSA Advertisements, 1980-1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - RSA Advertisements, 1980-1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - CAB Budget for Fiscal Year, 1981 May 1-1982 April 30 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Code of the Rent Stabilization Association of New York City, Inc., 1981 June (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - DHCR Report: Statistical Summary of Programs, 1982 March 31 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Rent Guidelines Board, Tenant Protection, Notes on Lawsuits, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - DHCR Newsclippings Memos and Speech by Yvonne Scruggs-Leftwich, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - NYC CAB Report 1981-1982, 1983 February (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - RSA Proposed Code and Correspondence, 1983 October-December (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - RSA Proposed Code and Memos, 1983 December 31 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - CAB, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - DHCR Memos and Briefs, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - CAB, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - CAB Memos and Tenant complaints, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - DHCR Correspondence, Minutes and Drafts, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - DHCR Memos, Correspondence and Manuals, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - DHCR Newsclippings, Memos and Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Cab Mailings to Board Members Concerning Tenant Complaints, 1984 January (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - RGB Expenditure Study, 1984 February 14 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - RSA Correspondence, 1984 February-March (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - DHCR Guide to Rent Regulations, 1984 December (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - DHCR Briefs and Sample Forms, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - DHCR News, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - DHCR Newsclippings and Memos, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Elimination of Rent Stabilization Association, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Proposals on Rent Stabilization Code, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Rent Stabilization Association Code, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Rent Stabilization Association Code Dispute, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Rent Stabilization Association Correspondence and Fact Sheets, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Rent Stabilization Code, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Rent Registration/ Tenant Complaint Forms, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - RSA and Assembly Analysis/ Correspondence regarding Rent Stabilization Code, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - DHCR Bulletins, 1984-1994 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - DHCR Bulletins and Reports, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - DHCR Report to Legislature on Office of Rent Administration, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Lawsuits against RGB, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Rent Stabilization Code Comments by DHCR, 1986 January 7 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - DHCR Press Releases, Renewal Forms and Opinion Pieces, 1986 March-July (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - The Council of the City of New York Int. No. 646, 1986 July 10 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - DHCR "The Uses and Limits of Rent Regulation, 1986 December 12 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - DHCR William Rowen Correspondence, 1986 December (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - DHCR Assorted Fact Sheets, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - DHCR Proposed Rent Stabilization Code, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - DHCR's Rent Stabilization Code, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - DHCR's Rent Stabilization Code, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal Proposed Rent Stabilization Code, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal Public Notices, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Law Suit: NYSTNC against William Eimicke, Commisioner DHCR, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Rent Stabilization Code Comments by DHCR, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Rent Stabilization Code Comments by DHCR, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - DHCR Updates on Rent Stabilization, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - News Articles and Testimonies from State Hearing on Performance of DHCR, 1987 March (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - NYSTNC Submissions to Rent Guidelines Board, 1987 May-June (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - DHCR Forms and Applications, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - DHCR Requests for Proposal for Administrative Services and Mailings, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Rent Guidelines Board Submissions, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - RGB Price Index, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - DHCR Advisory Opinion Listings, 1987-1992 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - DHCR Owner's Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes, 1988 January 15 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - DHCR Meeting Minutes with Manuals, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - DHCR Policy Recommendations, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - DHCR Tenants Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - NYS Housing Finance Agency Publications, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - RSA Correspondence, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - DHCR Funding and Policy Recommendations, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - DHCR Rent Terms Glossary and Applications, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - RSA Advertisements, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - DHCR Press Briefing Information Packet, 1989 January 19 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Rent Guidelines Board Testimony of Anthony J. Blackburn, 1989 February 28 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - NYC Board of Estimate Mailing and Newsclippings, 1989 March 20 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - DHCR Tenants Advisory Committee Agenda and Memos, 1989 May 11 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - DHCR Review of the Major Capital Improvement Plan, 1989 June 1 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - DHCR Mailings and Policy Drafts, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - DHCR Memos and Mailings, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - DHCR Tenants Advisory Committee Meeting Agendas, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - NYC Campaign Finance Board, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - DHCR Office of Rent Administration Policy Statement Listings, 1989-1993 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Appartment Price Indexes for Rent Stabilization Association, 1990 May 3 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - DHCR NYC Rent Stabilization Code, 1990 September (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - DHCR Agendas and Policy Statements, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - DHCR Agendas, Policy Drafts and Memos, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - DHCR Tenants Advisory Committee Agendas and Draft Manuals, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - NYSTNC Correspondence and Statements on RGB Price Index, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Price Index Correspondence with ANHD, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Rent Guidelines Board Eric Weinstock Testimony, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - RGB Price Indexes and Resumes, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - RSA Correspondence, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - DHCR Bulletins and Memos, 1990 September-1991 September (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - RSA Advertisements, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - RSA Advertisements, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - DHCR Program Bill 91-13A, 1991 January 24 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - DHCR Bulletins on Rent Dispute, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - DHCR Meeting Minutes and Policy Drafts, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - DHCR Tenant Advisory Committee Policy Drafts and Mailings, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - DHCR Tenant Advisory Committee Meetings, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - DHCR Tenant Advisory Committee Memos and Mailings, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - DHCR Tenant Protection Drafts and Mailings, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - RGB Submission to Rent Guidelines Association, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - DHCR Agendas, Bulletins and Memos, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - DHCR Fact Sheet Spanish Version, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - DHCR Memos and Mailings, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - DHCR Policy Drafts, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - DHCR Tenant Advisory Committee Agenda and Policy Drafts, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - NYSTNC 1992 Rent Guidelines Board Testimony (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - RGB Mail from Rent Stabilization Association, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - RGB Mail from Rent Stabilization Association, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - RGB Reports and Studies, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - RGB White Papers, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - DHCR Report to the Legislature, 1993 December (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - DHCR Publications, Memos and Juarez v. Wavecrest Management Lawsuit, 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - New York City Department of Housing Preservation and Development, 1994 February 10 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - DHCR Tenant Advisory Committee Meeting, 1994 April 7 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - DHCR Tenant Advisory Committee Meeting, 1994 June 2 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stabilized Rent is Biased, Threat to Adequate Housing in NYC, 1994 June (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - DHCR Tenant Advisory Committee Agendas and Drafts, 1994 June-November (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Council of the City of New York Memos and Policy, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - DHCR Tenant Advisory Committee Bulletins and Mailings, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - DHCR Tenant Advisory Committee Agenda, 1995 May 25 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - DHCR Tenant Advisory Committee Membership, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - RGB Correspondence, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence With Mayor Giuliani, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - RGB Propaganda Concerning Mayor Giuliani, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - RGB Propaganda Concerning Mayor Giuliani, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Rent Guidelines Board Index of Operating Costs, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Rent Guidelines Board Tenant Advocates Group, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - RGB Reports and Correspondence Concerning Lawsuit, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - The Rent Guidelines Board 1999 Mortgage Survey (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Rent Guidelines Board Appartment Orders and Comparisons, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - DHCR Guide to Housing Programs, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Legislative, 1973-2000, Undated; 3; 9.8
  The Legislative series is arranged chronolgically.
  The legislative series includes bill jackets, legislative memorandums, State Assembly and Senate vote records, correspondence regarding the legislation. The Tenants & Neighbors' legislative committee's related materials such as agendas, minutes, memoranda are represented in this series. Mitchell-Lama council legislation can be found in the legislative series.
  - Legislation, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Memorandums, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Assemblywoman Marie Runyon, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Memorandums and Rent and Eviction Regulation, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Memorandums, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - S. 7287, A. 9257, Legislative Memorandums In Opposition, 1976 February 17 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Drafts of Rent Regulation Bills, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - J-51 Tax Abatement, City Council Bills, 1976-1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - J-51 and New York City Department of Housing Preservation and Development, 1977-1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - J-51 State Authorization Section 489, Real Property Tax Law, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Mortgage Foreclosure Legislation, 1977-1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - J-51, 1977-1983 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Legislation and Related Materials, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Rent Control Issues, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Lobby Registration, 1977-1981 (Box 1, Folder 15-17)
  - Co-Op Conversion, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Rent Control Bill, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Mitchell-Lama Council, 1978-1984 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Bill Jackets and Memorandums, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Co-Op, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 22-24)
  - J-51 Background Research, 1979-1983 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Statewide Rent Control, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Legislation, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - ETPA/ Co-Op and Related Publications, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Proposed Statewide Rent and Eviction Control Bill, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - J-51 Background Research, 1990-1983 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - S. 1991 Landlords and "Personal Use", 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Legislation and Related Materials, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - Metropolitan Transportation Authority Property Transfer and Mortgage Recording Taxes, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Metropolitan Transportation Authority Tax and Appropriation Package, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Capital Gains Tax, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Co-Op and Related Newsclippings, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Legislation, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Intro 1192 Wallace Bill, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Co-Op Conversion Legislation, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Legislation, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Security Deposit Capital Pool, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Intro 1192 Including Legislative Memorandums, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Waterfront Development Bill, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - A. 2889 Apartment Hotels, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - J-51 Mitchell-Lama Housing, 1982-1987 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Co-Op Conversions Newspaper and Press Clippings, 1982-1987; Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Legislative Memorandums, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Co-Op Conversions, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - CO-Op Conversions Attorney General Regulations, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Omnibus Housing Act, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 22-23)
  - Omnibus Housing Act, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - Omnibus Housing Act Laws of 1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Omnibus Housing Act New Tenant Protection Law, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Omnibus Housing Act Materials on C.A.P., 1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Non-Profit Landlords COTONPIL Bill, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Post J-51, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - S. 2029-B, A. 2553-B Pet Bill, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - S. 1991 Restoration of NYC Rent Stabilization Code for Eviction, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Emergency Tenant Protection Act Renewal, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Emergency Tenant Protection Act Bill Drafting Commission, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Small Business Task Force Commercial Rent Regulation, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Extension to Upstate New York of Emergency Tenant Protection Act, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - A. 50 Protection for Tentants in Garden Type Maisonette Apartments in NYC, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Omnibus Banking Bills, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Legislative Plans and Related Materials, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Rules of the Senate, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - J-51 Major Capital Improvements, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Mobile Homes Bill Jackets and Memorandums, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Banking Laws, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - J-51 Legislative Memorandums and Draft Bills, 1983-1987 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Small Building Assessment, 1984 January (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Senate Chapter 403, 1984 February 7 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Tenant Alert from Assemblyman Pete Grannis, 1984 April (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Legislation and Related Materials, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 25-26)
  - Major Capital Improvements Legislation and Lawsuit, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Legislative Campaign Emergency Tenant Protection Act, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Omnibus Affordable Housing Act, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Legislation, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Memorandums Including James Garst Statements and Correspondence, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
  - Legislative Memorandums, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Single Room Occupancy (SRO) and J-51, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Price Index Campaign, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Housing Trust Fund, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Protection of Senior Citizens in Evictions, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Legislative Memorandums, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 10-11)
  - Single Room Occupancy Moratorium, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Information on Landlord Violations Including Correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Legislative Memorandums, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Legislation Housing Trust Fund, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Summary of 1985 Legislation (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - 1985 Legislature Last Weeks of Session (Box 4, Folder 17-18)
  - Testimony of Assemblyman Pete Grannis Board of Estimate Hearing, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Legislation, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 20-23)
  - A. 8107, A. 5576 Tenants and Not for Profit Organizations That Provide Housing, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Omnibus Housing Bill Extension of Rent Laws, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - California Legislature, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Program Bill, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Rules of the Senate, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Protection to Tenants in Rental Buildings Subject to Conversion to Cooperatives and Condominiums Bill, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Major Capital Improvements Memorandums, Bill Jackets, DHCR, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Housing Production with City Funds for Low and Moderate Income Families, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - J-51 Real Property Tax Law Bill and Memorandum, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Commission Expenditure Review Memorandum Report to the Legislature, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - NYS Assembly Correspondence, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - The Tax Law, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Reverse Mortgages, 1986-1990 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Court Merger Bill, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - J-51 Reform Coalition, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - "Bona Fide" Tenants State Assembly Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Legislation Omnibus Bill, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - J-51 Reform Coalition and Related Materials, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - New York State Tax Reform and Reduction Act of 1987 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Tax Reform, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Private Housing Finance Law, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Gay Life Partners Supreme Court Appelate Division, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Personal Use Evictions Legislation, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Legislation Including Bill Jackets and Descriptive Information Regarding Omnibus Bill, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Legislation, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Concept of Unconscionability and Related Bill Jackets, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Bill Jackets, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Federal Pre-payment Registration, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Legislation, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Attorney General Program Bill to Sponsor Duty to Cure Violations, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - A. 8972, A. 3054, A. 4953, A. 6795, A. 2726 Bill Jackets, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Coalition to Reform MCI, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - In Rem Early Warning Bill, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Rules of the Senate/ Rules of the Assembly, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Warehousing Campaign, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Governor's Program Bills and Related Information, 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 34-35)
  - New York City Rent Extenders, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - State Senator Election Campaign, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Legislation, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Major Capital Improvements Workshop Sponsored by NYSTNC, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Anti-Warehousing Campaign, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Anti-Warehousing Legislation and Materials on NYSTNC's Anti-Warehousing Commission, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Bill Jackets for Legislature Reforms, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Bill Jackets and Legislative Memorandums, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Memorandums, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 9-10)
  - Senior Citizen Rent Increase Exemption (SCRIE), 1988 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Legislative Memorandums on Vocate and Repair Issues, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Fair Share Housing Act A. 5064, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - New York City Council Intro 1329, Intro 1213, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - DHCR on Major Capital Improvements (MCI), 1989 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Private Housing Finance Law, Chapter 252, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Primary Residents Bill Jackets and Memorandums, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Bill Jackets, Memorandums and Related Newsclippings, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 18-19)
  - Assorted NYS Assembly and Cambridge, Massachusetts Materials, 1989; 1990 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Coalition to Reform MCI, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Rules of the Senate, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - New York State Attorney General Program Bills, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Major Capital Improvements (MCI), 1989-1992 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Property Tax Assessment, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Legislation, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Legislation and Memorandum in Support for MCI Reform, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Govenor's Program Bill Memorandum, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Queens, 1990-1992 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Attorney General Program Bills Addressed to Michael McKee, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 5-6)
  - Legislative Memorandums, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Govenor's Program Bill A. 7594, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Bawdy House Bill, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Warranty of Habitability and Other Legislation, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 10-11)
  - Warranty of Habitability Legislative Memorandums, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - DHRC Rent Administration and Rent Reform Bill, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Warranty of Habitability Weakener Veto, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - DHCR Rent Administration Reform and Equity Act, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Major Capital Improvements (MCI), 1991 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Legislation Including Testimony Before the Housing and Buildings Committee of NYC Council, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Comprehensive Housing Affordability Strategy (CHAS), 1991 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Legislation, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 19-20)
  - Legislation Including Memorandums for Mayor's Office, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Loans and Co-Op Conversions Including Bill Jackets, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Legislation, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Govenor Mario Cuomo's "Message to the Legislature" Report, 1992 January 8 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Luxury Decontrol Testimony, 1992 March 25 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Joint Public Hearing on the Federal Housing Oppurtunity for People Everywhere (HOPE) Program, 1992 July 16 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Legislation, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
  - Fundraising for Members of Legislature, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Memorandums, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - State Senator Dean Skelos, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Comprehensive Housing Affordability Strategy (CHAS), 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Invitations to Political Events and Fundraisers, 1992-1996 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - S. 5163 Legislative Memorandum, 1993 June 8 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - New York State Senate Rent Regulations Report, 1993 June 10 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Vacancy Decontrol S. 3424-A Legislative Memorandum, 1993 June 14 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - S. 4898-A, S. 4898-B Legislative Memorandums, 1993 June 21; 1993 June 28 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - S. 6177 Legislative Memorandum, 1993 July 5 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - A. 8859 Act to Ammend Emergency Tenant Protection Act, 1993 July 6 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Senate Bill Jackets 4900A and 4900B, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Legislation Extender, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - S. 3423 Conversion of Rental Residental Property to Cooperative or Condominium, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Congressional Hearing on Co-Op Financing, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Extender Includes Advisory Memorandums on Rent Registration and Rent Increase, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Legislative Memorandums in Opposition Sponsored by Either Senator Bruno or Senator Hannon, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Tenant Unity Coalition, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Legislation to Extend the Laws of 1973, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Legislation and Related Materials, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Rent Law Campaign, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Rent Extender Bill, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Bill Jackets, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Legislative Memorandums, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 1-3)
  - Legislation Including Memorandums, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 4)